Hey everybody, we are joined by Packers
head coach Matt LaFleur. Matt, welcome
and thanks for being here. Do you feel
you got you got better over the past
couple days? Yeah, absolutely. I think
anytime you can add talent to your
roster, it's an exciting time for the
Packers.
Now, you guys drafted six players
and four of them were defensive [music]
players. The first three defensive
players, is Jonathan Gannon, your new
defensive coordinator, a happy camper?
>> Oh, yeah. He's always happy, but he's
even happier now. So, I kind of had the
feeling that that's
the route we were going to go going into
the draft and certainly we had a lot of
high value marks on those
specific players and
we feel like we did a great job with
that.
Now, this past off season, a number of
changes on the coaching staff. How was
that group coming together and becoming
the team within a team that you have
needed to be? Yeah, I think it's been
great. I mean,
we've spent a lot of time in the meeting
room together and now it's our ability
to go out there and and teach whatever
we're going to teach to our players.
Matt, those first three defensive
players that you drafted, Colby Wooden,
[music]
Carrington Valentine, potential
contributors as rookies. How do you look
at that? Well, I think every guy that
comes in here has to earn their
opportunity, has to earn their their
reps. So,
but we feel good about those guys coming
in and competing right away.
With the addition of Trey Smack,
the last of your draft picks, the kicker
from Florida, is that a real deal
competition at that position? Yeah,
absolutely. Just like every other
position, you're always trying to to
bring in guys to compete and and make
your roster better and certainly we had
him as the highest rated kicker in the
draft and
we're lucky that he was still available
[music] when we got him.
Somewhere over the last couple of days,
you were able to find the time to resign
Jayden Reed. That is big stuff. I mean,
that young man is just a winner, isn't
he? He certainly is and I think you see
his contributions to our not only in our
offense, but our football team when he's
available. Certainly missed a lot of
time last last season with that
collarbone and
when he's not in the lineup, we feel
that. As things stand now,
you're looking at a revamped offensive
line. Sean Ryan at center, Anthony
Belton at right guard and then Jordan
Morgan at left tackle. Are you pretty
comfortable with that group? Yeah, I
think so. I think it's going to be an
important off season for those guys,
just like every off off season is, but
you know, just
to have five guys that you know where
[music] they're going to be cuz
certainly last year at this time we had
a left tackle competition
and [music]
then we went with
what we thought was our five best to go
out there and compete across the board
and
but Jordan a year ago showed us that he
is more than capable of holding that
position. Matt, can you give us any kind
of an update on your injured guys, in
particular, Micah Parsons, Tucker Kraft,
those types of individuals? Yeah, we've
been in in constant contact with those
guys and our medical staff and I would
say that they're coming along nicely,
but there's still a long road ahead of
them.
Are you
concerned at all about the backup
quarterback position? We've been
spoiled, no question with Malik, but are
you concerned at all right now at this
point? I wouldn't say concerned. I think
we're just trying to push these guys to
be their best and hopefully, you know,
of the two guys that we have, one of
these guys can take that step and and
really take a hold of that position.
Matt, you guys are involved in phase one
of the off season program right now. How
is that going and what is that all
about? Yeah, well, first of all, the
participation has been outstanding.
We've had the majority of our guys here
and they're just I love how they're
competing, coming in with a great
attitude and I think that's when that is
>> [music]
>> so important in terms of getting your
max results is you got to attack it the
right way and with the right mentality
and our guys are doing that.
I don't know about you, but I find it a
real exciting time in the year,
but I'm different.
Rookie camp coming up. You're looking
forward to it. I mean, you kind of get
the whole group together and it's kind
of cool. Yeah, that it's it'll be our
first exposure to these guys and really
the way we approach the rookie mini camp
is it's more of an onboarding process
for our guys, get them in, get them
acclimated to the building, get them
acclimated to their coaches, support
staff, the playbook, obviously each
other's an important component to that
and then we put them through a couple of
different workouts because it's
important because a week from that
rookie mini camp, they're
in with the vets in the phase two.
So, that gives them a chance to take
what they learn, go on their own for a
week, try to improve because a lot of
these guys have been training for the
combine, so they might not be in the
best football shape, but it gives them
an opportunity to kind of get a a jump
start on what's expected in phase two.
Matt, thank you. Appreciate it.
Absolutely. Thanks, Larry.